Learn English with Jennifer
Lesson 1: Greetings
Natasha is from Russia.
Natasha wants to learn English.
Jennifer teaches English.
Jennifer teaches Natasha.
Learn English with Jennifer and Natasha!
Hello Natasha
Hello Jennifer
How are you?
Fine. Thanks.
Fine thanks. Fine thank you.
Fine. Thank you.
How are you?
Good, good. Thank you.
I just said
Hello
and you said
How are you?
Listen.
Listen and repeat
How
How are you?
Hello
Hello Natasha, how are you?
Hello Jennifer, how are you?
Good.
Hello. Hello. How are you?
You can say
Fine thanks.
Can I ask you to move a little that way
How are you?
Listen, listen and repeat
Hello
How are you?
Fine thanks
Good
How are you?
So when I ask, I'm first
I say "how are you?"
You are second, and you say "how are you?"
So, listen. Listen.
Hello. - Hello. - How are you?
Fine thanks. How are you?
Do you hear the difference?
How are you?
This is me, Jennifer.
This is you, Natasha.
Hello.
How are you?
Fine thanks
Good. Thank you.
Listen and repeat.
Good
Not goood.
That's russian
Good.
Good. Let's not say that.
Good
Good. Thank you.
Listen
Thank you.
Good.
Good. Thank you.
So with good, relax: "Good".
Thank you.
Watch your tongue
Thank you
Good. Thank you.
Listen
Uhum, alright. Let's try again.
Hello Natasha.
Hello Jennifer.
How are you?
Fine. Thanks. How are you?
Good. Thank you.
Uhum, wonderful.
Thank you.